Tell everyone at home we'll be late tonight
So don't wait up
We've earned the right to celebrate
So forgive all my mistakes
Friends, for a handful of hours today
Let's walk the wayward path
Let's turn our backs on the world
Let's break all the rules
Out in the open
Making a sound
Drenched in red dye
Like true heroes, we'll dance
Jai Jai Shivshankar!
Carefree and wild
Let the colours fly!
We're raring to go
Carefree and wild
Let the colours fly!
Jai Jai Shivshankar!
Carefree and wild
Let the colours fly!
On a sweet melody
We keep in step
Let's move to the Desi beat
Forget all your inhibitions
Remember to get tipsy
Forget all your shame
Remember to dance
No one will be spared today
Everyone will dance the night away
That's two rounds for us
Let bank notes fly!
Let's get drunk and be merry
Like heroes, we'll dance
Jai Jai Shivshankar!
Carefree and wild
Let the colours fly!
We're raring to go
Carefree and wild
Let the colours fly!
Jai Jai Shivshankar!
Carefree and wild
Let the colours fly!
Jai Jai Shivshankar!
Carefree and wild
Let the colours fly!